Consumers' League of New York City Records 5307
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- New Jersey Consumers League - Newsletter, 1958-1960 (Box 36, Folder 16)
- New Jersey Consumers League - Publications and Statements, 1946-1959 (Box 36, Folder 17)
- New York City - Labor Department, 1960 (Box 37, Folder 1)
- New York City - CIO Council, 1955 (Box 37, Folder 2)
- New York City Federation of Women's Clubs, 1956 (Box 37, Folder 3)
- New York City Mayor's Office, 1959 (Box 37, Folder 4)
- New York State Legislators - Misc. Correspondence, 1959 (Box 37, Folder 5)
- New York State - Legislation - Misc., 1938-1950 (Box 37, Folder 6)
- New York State - Legislation - Government Employees, 1948 (Box 37, Folder 7)
- New York State - Legislation - State Legislative Service (Box 37, Folder 8)
- New York State - Legislation - Other Organizations, 1947 (Box 37, Folder 9)
- New York State - Legislation - Public Health, 1940 (Box 37, Folder 10)
- New York State - Legislation - Unemployment Insurance, 1948-1950 (Box 37, Folder 11)
- New York State - Legislation - Workmen's Compensation, 1939-1948 (Box 37, Folder 12)
- New York State - AFL-CIO, 1957-1959 (Box 37, Folder 13)
- New York State Association of Councils of Social Agencies, 1951-1959 (Box 37, Folder 14)
- New York State Congress of Parents and Teachers, 1954-1960 (Box 37, Folder 15)
- New York State Council of Churches, 1956-1960 (Box 37, Folder 16)
  Includes correspondence, releases, statements
- New York State Department of Commerce, 1956-1958 (Box 37, Folder 17)
- New York State Health Department - Migrant Labor Includes publications, 1944-1959 (Box 37, Folder 18)
- New York State Government Reports - Health Department -Semi-Monthly Reports, 1953 (Box 37, Folder 19)
- New York State Labor Department, 1947-1960 (Box 37, Folder 20)
- New York State Government Reports - Migrant Labor - Miscellaneous Reports, 1946-1953 (Box 38, Folder 1)
- New York State Department of Labor - Labor Legislation, 1950 (Box 38, Folder 2)
- New York State Department of Labor - Legislative Digest Session, 1950 (Box 38, Folder 3)
  Includes' Weekly Legislative Digest'
- New York State Department of Labor - Unemployment Insurance Reports, 1951-1958 (Box 38, Folder 4)
- New York State Department of Labor - Bill to License Labor Contractors, 1953 (Box 38, Folder 5)
- New York State Department of Labor - Board of Standards and Appeals, 1955 (Box 38, Folder 6)
- New York State Department of Labor - Budget, 1956 (Box 38, Folder 7)
- New York State Department of Labor - Reports - Migrant Labor - 'Child Fruit and Vegetable Pickers in NYS', 1950-1957 (Box 38, Folder 8)
- New York State Department of Labor - Child Labor, Laws Governing, 1947-1958 (Box 39, Folder 1)
- New York State Department of Labor - Conference on Migrant Labor - 'The Community and the Migratory Worker', 1959 (Box 39, Folder 2)
  Jan. 29, 1959
- New York State Department of Labor - Corsi Statement to Joint Legislative Committee on Industrial and Labor Conditions, 1953 (Box 39, Folder 3)
  10-Dec-53
- New York State Department of Labor - Cost of Living Surveys, 1950-1957 (Box 39, Folder 4)
- New York State Department of Labor - Division of Employment - Correspondences, 1957-1960 (Box 39, Folder 5)
- New York State Department of Labor - Unemployment Insurance - Division of Placement and Unemployment, Insurance, 1951-1959 (Box 39, Folder 6)
- New York State Department of Labor - Division of Placement and Unemployment Insurance - 'Farm and Food Processing Labor' Annual Reports, 1951-1958 (Box 39, Folder 7)
- New York State Department of Labor - Migrant Labor-Government Reports - Farm and Food Processing -Annual Reports, 1956-1957 (Box 39, Folder 8)
- New York State Department of Labor - Government Reports -'Labor Laws in Action on N.Y.S. Farms', 1958 (Box 39, Folder 9)
- New York State Department of Labor - CL Action -Organization and Administration of, 1947-1948 (Box 39, Folder 10)
- New York State Department of Labor - Statistics on Operations, 1952-1953 (Box 39, Folder 11)
- New York State Department of Labor - Statistics on Operations, 1950-1951 (Box 40, Folder 1)
- New York State Department of Labor - Statistics on Operations, 1954-1955 (Box 40, Folder 2)
- New York State Department of Labor - Statistics on Operations, 1956 (Box 40, Folder 3)
- New York State Department of Labor - Statistics on Operations, 1957-1958 (Box 40, Folder 4)
- New York State Department of Labor - Statistics on Operations, 1959 (Box 40, Folder 5)
- New York State Department of Labor - Research Memorandums - List of Special Labor News Memorandums, 1955 (Box 40, Folder 6)
- New York State Department of Labor - Women In Industry and Minimum Wage - Laws Governing, 1949-1951 (Box 40, Folder 7)
- New York State Disability Insurance - Legislation -Statements by E. Burns to State Democratic Committee and Joint Legislative Committee, 1949 (Box 40, Folder 8)
- New York State Disability Insurance - Acts Introduced to N.Y.S. Assembly, by J. Gans, 1950 (Box 40, Folder 9)
  Jan. 12, 1950
- New York State Disability Insurance - Proposed Legislation - General, 1947-1948 (Box 40, Folder 10)
- New York State Farm Labor - Contractors Supplying Farm Labor To Be Licensed, 1950 (Box 40, Folder 11)
- New York State - Interdepartmental Committee on Low Incomes, 1958 (Box 40, Folder 12)
- New York State - Legislation - Equal Pay, 1944-1948 (Box 40, Folder 13)
- New York State - Migrant Child Care Program, 1947-1955 (Box 40, Folder 14)
- New York State - Workmen's Compensation Board - Annual Reports, 1946-1951 (Box 41, Folder 1)
- New York League - Organization, 1941-1944 (Box 41, Folder 2)
- New York State - CIO - Correspondence, 1947-1951 (Box 41, Folder 3)
- New York Teachers Guild, 1958 (Box 41, Folder 4)
- New York Telephone Company, 1958 (Box 41, Folder 5)
- New York Times, 1956-1958 (Box 41, Folder 6)
- News Releases, 1957-1960 (Box 41, Folder 7)
- Newspapers - Correspondence With, 1957-1958 (Box 41, Folder 8)
- Night Work - N.Y.S. Laws re Affect on Families, 1946 (Box 41, Folder 9)
- Non-Profit Institutions - Employees of, Consumers League Action, 1959 (Box 41, Folder 10)
- Office Temporaries, 1959 (Box 41, Folder 11)
- Oneida-Kenwood-Sherrill Migrant Committee, 1953-1960 (Box 41, Folder 12)
  Includes photographs
- Ohio Consumers League Bulletins, publications, 1946-1959 (Box 41, Folder 13)
- Organizations - Agricultural Workers Union, 1952 (Box 41, Folder 14)
- Organizations - Americans for Democratic Action, 1948-1954 (Box 41, Folder 15)
- Organizations - Association of Catholic Trade Unionists, 1959 (Box 41, Folder 16)
- Organizations - Citizens Committee for Children of New York City -Report, 1960 (Box 41, Folder 17)
- Organizations - Citizens Union - Release, 1953 (Box 41, Folder 18)
- Organizations - C.I.O. 'Economic Outlook', 1948-1957 (Box 41, Folder 19)
- Organizations - Community Church of New York, 1950 (Box 41, Folder 20)
- Organizations - Consumer - Farmer Milk Cooperative, Inc., 1953 (Box 41, Folder 21)
- Organizations - Democratic State Committee, 1950-1953 (Box 41, Folder 22)
  Includes reports, program, correspondence
- Organizations - Girl Scouts of the U.S.A. (Box 41, Folder 23)
- Organizations - League for Industrial Democracy, 1954 (Box 41, Folder 24)
- Organizations - League of Women Voters, 1956-1958 (Box 41, Folder 25)
- Organizations - Liberal Party, 1951-1958 (Box 41, Folder 26)
- Organizations - National Advisory Committee on Farm Labor, 1958-1960 (Box 42, Folder 1)
- Organizations - National Association for the Advancement of Colored People, 1953 (Box 42, Folder 2)
- Organizations - National Association of Manufacturers, 1952 (Box 42, Folder 3)
- Organizations - National Child Labor Committee, 1948-1960 (Box 42, Folder 4)
- Organizations - National Council of the Churches of Christ in the U.S. Division of Home Missions, 1951-1957 (Box 42, Folder 5)
- Organizations - National Council on Agricultural Life and Labor, 1954-1960 (Box 42, Folder 6)
- Organizations - National Planning Association, 1953 (Box 43, Folder 1)
- Organizations - National Sharecroppers Fund, Inc., 1949-1958 (Box 43, Folder 2)
- Organizations - National Social Welfare Assembly, 1948 (Box 43, Folder 3)
- Organizations - N.Y.S. AFL-CIO, 1953-1960 (Box 43, Folder 4)
- Organizations - N.Y.S. Congress of Parents and Teachers, Inc., 1955 (Box 43, Folder 5)
- Organizations - N.Y.S. Council of Churches, 1958-1959 (Box 43, Folder 6)
- Organizations - Public Affairs Committees Inc., 1953 (Box 43, Folder 7)
- Organizations - Women's City Club of NYC (Box 43, Folder 8)
- Organizations - Women's Trade Union League (N.Y. and National), 1947-1953 (Box 43, Folder 9)
  Includes scattered issues of the 'Bulletin', correspondence, annual reports
- Organizations - Workers Defense League (Box 43, Folder 10)
- Pennsylvania Citizen's Committee on Migrant Labor (Box 43, Folder 11)
- Pennsylvania Department of Labor and Industry (Box 43, Folder 12)
- President of the U.S. (Box 43, Folder 13)
- President's Commission on the Health Needs of the Nation (Box 43, Folder 14)
- President's Committee on Migratory Labor (Box 43, Folder 15)
- Press Clipping Service (Box 43, Folder 16)
- Publicity, 1945-1946 (Box 43, Folder 17)
- Renewals (Box 43, Folder 18)
  Includes letters of membership renewals
- Republican State Committee (Box 43, Folder 19)
- Residence Requirement (Box 43, Folder 20)
- Resident Requirement - Reference Materials (Box 43, Folder 21)
- Retail Drug Employees Union (Box 43, Folder 22)
- Robinson, Jackie (Box 43, Folder 23)
- Senate Sub-Committee on Labor and Public Welfare Hearings on Migratory Labor, 1952 (Box 44, Folder 1)
- Senate Sub-Committee on Migratory Labor Correspondence, statements (Box 44, Folder 2)
- Senators (U.S.) From N.Y.S. (Box 44, Folder 3)
- Social Security (Box 44, Folder 4)
  Includes statement to Ways and Means Committee from CL
- Social Welfare Department - N.Y.S. Correspondence (Box 44, Folder 5)
- Social Welfare Department - N.Y.S. - Registration of Non-Profit Organizations (Box 44, Folder 6)
  Includes correspondence, directories
- State Charities Aid Association (Box 44, Folder 7)
  Report, statement, correspondence
- State Department, N.Y.S. (Box 44, Folder 8)
- Statewide Citizens' Committee on Seasonal Farm Labor (Frye Group) (Box 44, Folder 9)
- Taxes Tax forms and correspondence (Box 44, Folder 10)
- Telegrams re Legislation (Box 44, Folder 11)
- T.V. Programs Arrangements for program on migratory labor In N.Y.S. (Box 44, Folder 12)
- Unemployment Insurance - Miscellaneous Materials Publications, correspondence (Box 44, Folder 13)
- Unemployment Insurance Correspondence, printed legislative bills (Box 45, Folder 1)
- Unemployment Insurance Joint Legislative Committee Hearings, 1957 (Box 45, Folder 2)
  Fall 1957
- Unemployment Insurance Joint Legislative Committee on Unemployment Insurance Publications (Box 45, Folder 3)
- Unemployment Insurance CL policy statements (Box 45, Folder 4)
- Unemployment Insurance - Requests for League Statement Following N.Y. Times Editorial, 1958 (Box 45, Folder 5)
  24-Feb-58
- United Neighborhood Houses of N.Y., Inc. (Box 45, Folder 6)
- U.S. Department of labor Statements, correspondence, publications (Box 45, Folder 7)
- U.S. Department of Labor, Bureau of Labor Standards - Annual Digest of State and Federal Labor Legislation (Box 45, Folder 8)
- U.S. Department of Labor, Bureau of Labor Standards - National Conference on Labor Legislation (Box 45, Folder 9)
- U.S. Department of Labor, Children's Bureau Correspondence, 1945-1946 (Box 45, Folder 10)
- U.S. Department of Labor, Division of Labor Standards Publications, correspondence (Box 45, Folder 11)
- U.S. Department of Labor, Wage and Hours and Public Contracts Division (Box 46, Folder 1)
  N.Y. Region Publications
- U.S. Department of Labor, Women's Bureau (Box 46, Folder 2)
  Regional Helen B. Sater
- U.S. Department of Labor, Women's Bureau (Box 46, Folder 3)
- U.S. Department of Labor, Women's Bureau (Box 46, Folder 4)
  Miscellaneous publications
- U.S. Department of Labor, Women's Bureau (Box 46, Folder 5)
  'Facts on Women Workers'
- U.S. Department of Labor, Women's Bureau (Box 46, Folder 6)
  Household Employees Material
- U.S. Department of Labor, Women's Bureau (Box 46, Folder 7)
  Minimum Wage Material
- U.S. Federal Security Agency (Box 46, Folder 8)
  Social Security Administration - Bureau of Old Age and Survivors Insurance Publications
- Volunteers (Unpaid Work by Minors) (Box 47, Folder 1)
- We Answer Phones (Box 47, Folder 2)
- Westchester Childrens Association (Box 47, Folder 3)
- White House Conference on Children and Youth (Box 47, Folder 4)
- WMCA - Radio Station (Box 47, Folder 5)
- Women's City Club of New York, Inc. (Box 47, Folder 6)
- Women Hours - light Work (N.Y.S.), 1950 (Box 47, Folder 7)
  Legislative bills and correspondence
- Women Workers - Employment, N.Y.S., 1944-1945 (Box 47, Folder 8)
- Women Workers - 'Facts on Women Workers' - Women's Bureau, U.S. Department of Labor (Box 47, Folder 9)
- Women Workers - Hours, 1944-1946 (Box 47, Folder 10)
  Correspondence - Rose Schneiderman (Women's Trade Union League), publication
- Consumers' League Collected Pamphlets, 1893-1915 (Box 48, Folder 1)
  Bound volume
  - Item 1: White List, 1893 (Box 48, Folder 1)
    1p.
    Format: Pamphlet.
  - Item 2: Extracts from Reports of the Governing Board for the Years 1892 and 1893. New York: The League (Box 48, Folder 1)
    4p.
  - Item 3: Lowell, Mrs. Charles Russell, Consumers' League. Boston: Consumers' League of Boston, 1898 (Box 48, Folder 1)
    34p.
  - Item 4: Consumers' League and Some Of Its Doings, 1898 (Box 48, Folder 1)
  - Item 5: Report on the State of Charities and Visiting Committee, 1900 (Box 48, Folder 1)
    11p.
  - Item 6: What Can You Do to Check Christmas Cruelties, 1904 (Box 48, Folder 1)
  - Item 7: Our Working Child. New York: The League, 1906 (Box 48, Folder 1)
    10p.
  - Item 8: Report for the Year Ending February 27, 1907. New York: The League (Box 48, Folder 1)
    44p.
  - Item 9: Summary of New York Laws for Working Women. New York: The League, 1907 (Box 48, Folder 1)
    6p.
  - Item 10: Historical Sketch of th Pioneer Consumers' League, 1908 (Box 48, Folder 1)
    24p.
  - Item 11: Report for the Year Ending February 27, 1909. New York: The League (Box 48, Folder 1)
    51p.
  - Item 12: McVickar, Mrs. Robert. Work of State Consumers' League. New York: New York State Consumers' League, 1909 (Box 48, Folder 1)
  - Item 13: Child Labor Bills In Danger at Albany, 1909 (Box 48, Folder 1)
  - Item 14: White List of Firms Complying With the Mercantile Law, 1909 (Box 48, Folder 1)
    2p. Brooklyn Auxiliay of the Consumers' League of the City of New York
  - Item 15: White List of Firms Complying With the Laws, 1910 (Box 48, Folder 1)
  - Item 16: Some of the Means Used to Better Industrial Conditions for Women and Children, 1910 (Box 48, Folder 1)
    8p.
  - Item 17: Sergeant, Elizabeth Shepley. Toilers of the Tenements: Where the Beautiful Things of the Great Shops Are Made. New York: New York State Consumers' League, 1910 (Box 48, Folder 1)
    18p.
  - Item 18: Clark, Sue Ainslie and Edith Wyatt. Working-Girls' Budgets: Based Upon Individual Stories of Self -Supporting Girls. New York: Consumers' League of the City of New York, 1910 (Box 48, Folder 1)
    20p.
  - Item 19: Exhibit of the Comsumers League and the Child Labor Committee, 1910 (Box 48, Folder 1)
    2p. Teachers College, Columbia University, New York
  - Item 20: Bulletin no.1, 1911 (Box 48, Folder 1)
    1p. January 30, 1911. The New York State Consumers' League
  - Item 21: Bulletin no.2, 1911 (Box 48, Folder 1)
    1p. May 1911. The New York State Consumers' League
  - Item 22: Bulletin no.3, 1911 (Box 48, Folder 1)
    1p. October 1911. The New York State Consumers' League
  - Item 23: Consumers' League, Buffalo. Annual Report for the Year Ending December 1911. Buffalo: The League, 1912 (Box 48, Folder 1)
    26p.
  - Item 24: Annual Report for the Year Ending December 1912. Buffalo: The League, 1913 (Box 48, Folder 1)
    21p.
  - Item 25: Is There Any Hope of Enforcing the Law, 1913 (Box 48, Folder 1)
  - Item 26: Report, June 1910 to February 26, 1913. New York: The League (Box 48, Folder 1)
    54p.
  - Item 27: The Consumers' League of New York State: What It Is -What It Does - Why It Is Needed. New York: The League, 1913 (Box 48, Folder 1)
  - Item 28: Syracuse Consumers' League Annual Meeting, 1913 (Box 48, Folder 1)
  - Item 29: Five Thousand Dollars for the Consumers' League of New York State, 1913 (Box 48, Folder 1)
    3p.
  - Item 30: Our Working Girls: How They Do It, 1913 (Box 48, Folder 1)
  - Item 31: Appeal on Behalf of Our Working Women, Our Wage-Earning Children Our Infant Wards, Your Own Homes, 1913 (Box 48, Folder 1)
    2p.
  - Item 32: Laws Every Consumer Should Know and Make Known, 1914 (Box 48, Folder 1)
  - Item 33: The Consumers' League of New York State: What It Is -What It Does - Why It Is Needed. New York: The League, 1914 (Box 48, Folder 1)
  - Item 34: Prayers Written for the Consumers' League, 1914 (Box 48, Folder 1)
  - Item 35: The Consumers' League, 1914 (Box 48, Folder 1)
  - Item 36: The Consumers' League, 1914 (Box 48, Folder 1)
  - Item 37: Consumers' League Label, 1914 (Box 48, Folder 1)
  - Item 38: A Woman's Work Is Never Done, 1915 (Box 48, Folder 1)
  - Item 39: The Consumers' League: The Why and the Wherefore, 1915 (Box 48, Folder 1)
  - Item 40: Prayer Written for the Consumers' League, 1915 (Box 48, Folder 1)
  - Item 41: Bibliography, 1915 (Box 48, Folder 1)
    12p.
  - Item 42: Twenty-Five Years of the Consumers' League of The City of New York, 1915 (Box 48, Folder 1)
    39p.
  - Item 43: Vacation Time: Remember the Department Store Girls, 1915 (Box 48, Folder 1)
  - Item 44: Laws Every Consumer Should Know and Make Known, 1915 (Box 48, Folder 1)
    5p.
  - Item 45: The Work of the Consumers' League of the City of New York, 1915 (Box 48, Folder 1)
    28p.
- Consumers' League Collected Pamphlets, 1916-1927 (Box 48, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Campaigning Against Industrial Evils, 1916 (Box 48, Folder 2)
  - Item 2: Campaigning Against Industrial Evils: The Report of the Consumers' League of the City of New York, 1916 (Box 48, Folder 2)
    30p.
  - Item 3: The Cost of Clean Clothes in Terms of Health: A Study of Laundries and Laundry Workers in New York City, 1916 (Box 48, Folder 2)
    96p.
  - Item 4: Behind the Scenes in a Restaurant: A Study ot 1017 Women Restaurant Employees, 1916 (Box 48, Folder 2)
  - Item 5: Relief for Restaurant Workers, 1917 (Box 48, Folder 2)
  - Item 6: Club Programs and National Service, 1917 (Box 48, Folder 2)
  - Item 7: Be a Neighbor but in the Modern Way, 1917 (Box 48, Folder 2)
  - Item 8: Give Back to the Women Wor Work: The Spirit of Life, 1917 (Box 48, Folder 2)
  - Item 9: Why Not Begin Your Christmas Shopping Now, 1917 (Box 48, Folder 2)
  - Item 10: The Consumers' League of New York State, 1917 (Box 48, Folder 2)
  - Item 11: Shopping Is Power, 1917 (Box 48, Folder 2)
  - Item 12: Is There Any Hope of Enforcing the Law, 1917 (Box 48, Folder 2)
  - Item 13: Who Will Put "Rest In Restaurants", 1917 (Box 48, Folder 2)
  - Item 14: Sixteenth Annual Meeting of the Consumers' League of New York State, 1917 (Box 48, Folder 2)
  - Item 15: Use Your Shopping Power: You Can Help Get Good Working Conditions in Stores and Factories, 1917 (Box 48, Folder 2)
  - Item 16: Piano Recital by Guiomar Novacs, 1917 (Box 48, Folder 2)
  - Item 17: Campaigning Against Industrial Evils: The Report of the Consumers' League of the City of New York, 1917 (Box 48, Folder 2)
  - Item 18: Dear Member of the New York State Consumers' League, 1917 (Box 48, Folder 2)
  - Item 19: The Consumers' League of New York State, 1917 (Box 48, Folder 2)
  - Item 20: What Is the Consumers' League?, 1917 (Box 48, Folder 2)
  - Item 21: The Consumers' League, 1917 (Box 48, Folder 2)
  - Item 22: How Manufacturing in Tenements Endangers Public Health and Breaks Down the Family, 1917 (Box 48, Folder 2)
    14p.
  - Item 23: Campaigning Against Industrial Evils, 1917 (Box 48, Folder 2)
  - Item 24: If You Agree Help Us: A Post-War Program, 1918 (Box 48, Folder 2)
  - Item 25: Towards a New Industrial Era, 1918 (Box 48, Folder 2)
    25p.
  - Item 26: Campaigning Against Industrial Evils, 1918 (Box 48, Folder 2)
  - Item 27: 1918 Legislative Program of the Consumers' League of New York City (Box 48, Folder 2)
  - Item 28: If You Agree Help Us: A Post-War Program, 1919 (Box 48, Folder 2)
  - Item 29: Is This Living?, 1919 (Box 48, Folder 2)
    15p.
  - Item 30: The Case for Special Legislation for Women Workers, 1919 (Box 48, Folder 2)
  - Item 31: A New Day for the Colored Women Worker, 1919 (Box 48, Folder 2)
  - Item 32: Annual Report 1919, 1920 (Box 48, Folder 2)
  - Item 33: Do You Know These Laws? If Not, Why Not?, 1919 (Box 48, Folder 2)
  - Item 34: Annual Repor 1920, 1921 (Box 48, Folder 2)
  - Item 35: Women and Machines, 1921 (Box 48, Folder 2)
    14p. Mary Van Kleeck
  - Item 36: Less Than A Living Wage, 1921 (Box 48, Folder 2)
    9p.
  - Item 37: Behind the Scenes in a Hotel, 1922 (Box 48, Folder 2)
    47p.
  - Item 38: Consumers' Cooperative Societies in New York State, 1922 (Box 48, Folder 2)
  - Item 39: Constitution and By-Laws of the Consumers' League of New York, 1922 (Box 48, Folder 2)
  - Item 40: Preliminary Program of Industrial Institute for Central New York, 1922 (Box 48, Folder 2)
  - Item 41: Education for Industry: Training Course for Labor Inspectors, 1925 (Box 48, Folder 2)
  - Item 42: Have Your Done Your Christmas Shopping?, 1926 (Box 48, Folder 2)
  - Item 43: Questions and Answers, 1926 (Box 48, Folder 2)
  - Item 44: These Are the Facts, 1926 (Box 48, Folder 2)
  - Item 45: Annual Report 1926-1927 (Box 48, Folder 2)
  - Item 46: Facts About the Consumers' League of New York, 1927 (Box 48, Folder 2)
  - Item 47: The Forty Eight Hour Law: Do Working Women Want It? (Box 48, Folder 2)
    40p.
  - Item 48: Annual Report 1927-1928 (Box 48, Folder 2)
- News clippings, 1945-1946 (Box 48, Folder 3)
- The Consumers' League Bulletin, 1919-1920 (Box 48, Folder 4)
  v.9:no.3 (1919:Dec.) and v.10:no.1 (1920:Feb.)
- Brooks, John Graham. The Consumers' League. Boston: National Consumers' League, 1900 (Box 49, Folder 1)
- Consumers' League, Eastern Pennsylvania. Colored Women as Industrial Workers in Philadelphia. Philadelphia: The League, 1920 (Box 49, Folder 2)
  49 p.
- Consumers' League, Eastern Pennsylvania. Tragedies in Industry: Disease of Occupation in Pennsylvania, 1928 (Box 49, Folder 2a)
  23 p.
- A Proposed Act to Regulate the Employment of Women [in the] Commonwealth of Pennsylvania. Philadelphia: The League, 1913 (Box 49, Folder 3)
  17 p.
- Raising the Standard of Work by Raising the State of the Worker; Some Phases of the Work of the Consumers' League of Eastern Pennsylvania, 1917-1919. Philadelphia: The League (Box 49, Folder 4)
- Consumers' League, Massachusetts, Some Types of Industrial Poisening. Boston: The League, 1929 (Box 49, Folder 5)
  44 p.
- Consumers' League, National. The Blanket Equality Bill Proposed by the National Woman's Party for State Legislatures - Why It Should Not Pass. New York: The League, 1922 (Box 49, Folder 6)
  8pp
- Can Money Compensate A Crippled Child? New York: The League, 1920 (Box 49, Folder 7)
  4 p.
- The Cave Report on the British Trade Board Acts, 1909-1922: The Success of Minimum Wage Legislation. New York, The League, 1909- 1923 (Box 49, Folder 8)
  108 p.
- Clarifying the Constitution by Amendment. New York: The League, 1936 (Box 49, Folder 9)
  22 p.
- The Conference on the Breakdown of Industrial Standards. New York: The League, 1932 (Box 49, Folder 10)
  46 p.
- The Conference on Labor Law Administration, New York: The League, 1935 (Box 49, Folder 11)
  27 p.